hello
my name is green and we are heading
straight over to the shopping district
because i have arranged well actually
it's that way we have arranged to meet
up with iskall and false who last
episode we decided it was a draw but
yeah i'm going to change
the outcome and i'm going to explain why
right now guys where's this girl false
um
hello welcome to my head hunt
i don't sound like that
that's a terrible accent
what do you mean what do you mean
it's just totally me it's totally green
that's rude you know trying to
impersonate someone else that's not nice
why is that a scarf i would never
impersonate anybody especially if they
don't have an accent that i can do
so i've asked you guys to come here
because of the green head hunt results
which i did last episode but
the actual scoring needs to be changed
slightly so i've put a couple of signs
here saying false you are the winner the
the 100 you have won however the scoring
ended up being
197 points to iskal and 192 points to
false which means that would put you in
second place
but it turns out that iskall actually
got 10 points for complimenting me
during my inspection of his fault
i love your scarf
it
turns out iskal that you weren't even
there there was somebody in your vault
doing an impeccable impression of your
voice it was it was amazing i thought it
was really you so unfortunately i'm
going to have to deduct those 10 points
so that means 187 points to you and 192
to false meaning she went that means
however i still stand by what i said
that iskal had the best vault out of
everybody on the server he put the most
effort in so he did there's a bit of a
compromise here iskals going to get one
of the items from this chest but false
is going to decide which one it is
oh
okay there's a there's a lot of boxes of
goodies in there 64 diamonds seems
pretty good i mean i'm just saying yeah
no that that that's that's calling to me
right there
i think oh well what do you need do you
need any cr any material okay so false
you gave you gave iskal the box of
gravel right i did yeah that was nice so
that's all that all belongs to you and
the the crowning prize in there is the
green will help you with any pranks so
oh yes thank you no i won't do a prank
for you and it won't be a prank on me
those are the two exceptions i won't do
it solely by myself and it can't be a
prank against me
that works
all right uh so you can take your
goodies and congratulations on
officially winning the green head hunt
i'm never doing this ever again
can i just say it's a very lovely scarf
and there are more things oh she took it
all
i hate your scarf it's gone
thanks for participating
thank you for the headache thank you see
ya now i'm not afraid to admit it guys
but
i messed up when i did the points i gave
iskal far too many more than he deserved
and for reasons that were actually wrong
as well
and i cut down false's points for
reasons that i interpreted differently
so let me explain so i gave false minus
points for being a poor criminal because
in my mind i wanted to see massive raids
of people's vaults taking everything
that's what i kind of in i kind of
encouraged everybody to do
however
with false she actually only took a few
now i thought she was just being a
gentleman
or a gentle woman it turns out she was
just skimming enough of the top
so that the other person wouldn't notice
that their heads are gone at all which
is absolutely genius and devious the
other thing is that false actually
was the one that introduced the chorus
fruit mechanism to get into iskall's
vault so
100 percent
she should have won
hands down now that's not to say that
everyone else didn't find many heads
like tango had 300 heads before he was
unfairly raided so just because she got
the most doesn't mean that she actually
ended up with the actual most green
heads but she played the game fairly
and very well so i obviously have
changed it so that she is the full
winner but
iskall definitely gets something
something for the way that he made his
vault excellent but it's over now it's
all sorted all fixed and it was a
brilliant game and lots of fun so
no more to say about that i think but
you might have noticed that i've flown
over here to the creeper farm and it
wasn't for no reason i want to go
and borrow
some of this
so i'm going to just
take a few shulker boxes worth now i'm
absolutely sure that he won't mind at
all now i went and got myself a little
note
just so i could let him know that i
needed this for a thing oh wow his
system's blocked up anyway he needs
someone to
empty this anyway so we're gonna fill up
a few shulker boxes and i'm gonna make
sure that i overpay him for it so that
he doesn't get upset the only reason i
don't really want to tell him is because
i don't think that he would approve of
how i plan on using this
mumbo did say i could take whatever i
needed from these machines so i'm going
to pay him one diamond per stack which i
feel is more than fair considering i
actually helped and he actually gave me
permission to take whatever i needed
from this
however because i'm actually going to
use this in another shop of mine
uh oh well it's not really a shop it's a
service
it's only fair that i pay him his jews
because i plan on using all of this
for a shop and so it's only fair that i
actually share some of the money that
i'm going to be making i don't know if
anyone's going to use this but we're
going to go and make it right now i
think i've prepared everything we're
going to need and it's a lot of dark
blocks and i think most of you might
work out what i'm up to especially as
you see this block here
now i'm going to use a lot of my sand
a lot of my sand to make
well you guys know exactly what i plan
on making sum t
n
t
this is actually the first time that i'm
crafting it myself i believe it's been a
long time my friend
i i absolutely love tnt it's the most
destructive block there is now we're not
actually going to be selling this tnt
and that's quite important
we are just going to be offering our
services as a professional and i mean
professional demolition man
i think that is a decent amount of tnt
to get us started and this should be
enough
to be able to make the shop that we want
the hard bit is going to be finding a
space in the shopping district for this
because boy oh boy
is it getting a little cramped in here
actually there might be a little
actually this might be a decent space if
no one has taken this there's a chest
here with nothing in it no signage
telling me
that i can't build here this is
definitely in the shopping district and
i don't need anything too big since this
is just a service based shop now
what i'm making is obviously the
demolition shop okay but i want this to
be as naturally generated as possible i
want to give a proper
idea of what this might look like
so we're going to make this not with our
hand
but with our new tnt now i'm going to go
very conservative i don't want to blow
up anything around me so i'm going to go
for some controlled explosions here now
this
is probably a terrible idea
probably a very terrible idea and this
will give us a good chance to practice
practice our controlled explosions
all right here we go first tnt use
of hermitcraft
oh i thought it wasn't going to go off
i was like oh that did uh that did a lot
more than i thought
oh boy that was only five tnt
why did it take so long oh well well
that was um i'm glad i didn't use any
more than that now if you're wondering
whether it's a terrible terrible idea
for me to be playing with tnt
you would be absolutely right those of
you that have been watching my channel
for a while
know that me plus tnt is no good at all
i fear for the person that really needs
this service i don't know how many
people actually need something blowing
up
but
my goodness do i know how to blow stuff
up the crux of it of course has to be
obsidian in the middle and then i kind
of want to make it seem like it's
scorched all the way around so it looks
like a crater now i've never made
anything quite like this but i
understand the theory behind it i'm just
a little worried that i don't have the
resources i need to finish it off
i also brought along one of my very
valuable wither skeleton skulls to make
it look like someone actually got
scorched here
i've officially run out of the resources
that i need but this is starting to come
together the palette kind of works it's
just all of this greenery has to go
there'll be no greenery here so i'm
trying to make it look like there's been
an explosion there and everything that
was in the blast radius kind of has died
so i've got a bit of podzol and then i'm
making some pathway blocks as well
there's something amiss here
why is that name
down near me what
was she spying on me is there even a
shop there
oh yeah that totally is
i'm so paranoid and i think that
is what i'm gonna call it for now i
think that's a pretty good crater and
i've i've run out of a lot of resources
so it might look a bit janky here and
there and that's just because i've run
out of a specific color that's why i've
mixed so many in together maybe the
netherrack is a little bit
higgledy-biggly maybe i can uh rearrange
some of these blocks to make it better
distributed but other than that i think
it looks pretty good but now we actually
have to put the shot bit in here oh and
of course we have to add some fire right
gonna leave a chest here and that's
basically it i'm gonna go and write a
book now and explain how it's gonna work
and you know it actually looks pretty
decent from it definitely attracts your
attention that's for sure maybe i'm just
looking at it but if i'm flying over
that really stands out because it looks
like a meteor has hit the shopping
district and that's kind of what i want
so in order to light this up i am going
to create some
everlasting fire
to make it seem like this place recently
hit the dust the only problem i'm having
here is i have no idea what to charge
for it part of me thinks one diamond for
every five tnt use because it involves
mining sand getting the gun powder
crafting it
but i feel like i don't actually make
much profit if i have to pay mumbo a
diamond for every stack of gunpowder i
use
the math might be a little bit off
all right so in the chest i've got a
book that says a bad idea by green and
it says green's demolition shop totally
not an excuse to use tnt
as you can see i am an expert at blowing
stuff up such as this part of the
shopping district i offer you my
services and my tnt to blow up anything
at your request the pricing is one
diamond per five tnt used absolute
bargain pretty sure i make a loss on it
or maybe a slight profit
i may just want to blow stuff up actions
can be performed anonymously please
contact oh i missed a t in there and
i've signed up it's too late
please contact me or leave a book with
payment with instructions all right
there we go that is the very bad idea
and
i want to see how tempted people can get
so i'm going to put tnt there and what
i'm going to do is put some redstone
dust like so
and then
add temptation in the form of a lever
i'll tell you what's more valuable to me
at the moment is emeralds i don't think
that i actually want to charge diamonds
anymore you know
i think i'm going to change my pricing
on everything
to emeralds because
let's be honest here when you die
you have to go over to impulse's shop to
make all of this stuff now i've got lots
of diamonds i have zero emeralds i think
i'm gonna change my pricing a little bit
maybe not here but maybe over at the
quartz shop i will do that
no no no no no no no no
oh oh my god oh my goodness oh my
goodness oh my goodness that could have
been
the biggest disaster
oh boy
no
bad
that's my job look what that went
through him
oh
that could have been you know what this
could very well be a very very bad idea
oh my goodness
okay we should light this place up i
feel
okay so that is it that is the
demolition shop and i think it's not my
best work but i've never made a crater
quite like that before and also you have
to remember that i didn't have as much
obsidian as i would have normally used
this is all i had and i think i wanted
to put it in the center it's it's i
think it's come out pretty well everyone
should know what it is it's definitely
going to drag some eyes to it to check
it out and i wonder who our first
customer is going to be now no one on
this server is going to
employ me to blow up someone else's base
but they might employ me to blow up a
big hole or some sort but i tell you
what we need to do is actually practice
the use of the tnt we can't offer up our
services it's been i'm a bit rusty you
know it's been nearly seven months since
i had a good go at this
and well since we've got so much tnt
i think that we should put our skills to
the test i also think this would be a
great opportunity
to collect a lot of gravel i don't
actually know how much damage this will
do maybe we should do an experiment
because i don't actually want to blow up
any of the gravel
i think this is very doable okay
so what we're gonna do one two three
four five six i'm gonna place a bunch of
tnt
in a line
i'm pretty sure it's much faster just to
use a shovel but it's much less fun as
well all right
let's give it a go
and they're off
and
[Music]
well the redstone signal didn't quite
make it but we got a good explosion
yeah this is not effective at all this
is not effective it's not efficient is
the main thing
but well since we're here
okay that didn't leave much gravel at
all
yeah i think there's a reason no one
uses tnt for this kind of job
and i think it's because it doesn't
leave much left over
much much simpler just to use a shovel
something i've always wanted to do in
survival but i've
never actually done and i feel kind of
naughty doing something like this on the
hermitcraft server but
i just want to make a bit of mayhem i
know i'm wasting a lot of my tnt but
you know i'm 33 episodes into this
series and i haven't had fun with tnt at
all why not have a little bit of fun now
that i've got my hands on my favorite
block
and
we're off
oh dear here we go
it's hurting it it lagged me into the
floor
whoa
well what did we get from that hey
there's some emeralds
two stacks of tnt was totally worth it
one emerald come on
well
that was a total waste of resources
but
i think we've had enough fun with the
tnt for now but something else i want to
do is i've gathered up a lot of the
gravel sand that i've been hoarding and
not really using so i've decided that
i'm going to sell it especially as
rendog is online and i know that he
needs it way more than i do so what
we're going to do is change the pricing
that i mentioned earlier so in here yet
zeddaff is still banned
still banned
i wonder if he's actually sold any whoa
that sounded like a creeper it was a
creeper
man i am so lucky if i didn't go and
check uh my shop would have been a goner
get out of here
as i was saying i wonder if he's
actually sold any he's actually still
selling quartz
unbelievable
i've sold
i i must have sold more anyway doesn't
matter
we are gonna shift all of this gravel
and sand
but we're gonna change the pricing
we got a double chest here a double
chest there it's all very messy and a
single chest there that is quite a lot
of stuff
now i need to take
oh my goodness
all right let's rename these shall we
and this will also mean that zeddaff can
get unbanned because he won't be able to
buy them easily i don't care if he buys
them and sells them on for diamonds i
want some emeralds
one emerald for one stack
there we go
maybe that's too expensive but if they
want this grindy stuff
then they have to pay
so the new price is officially an
emerald for a stack and hopefully i will
amass enough emeralds so that the next
time that i die
i will be able to save myself a lot of
bother
when i'm back at impulse's place
spending a load of diamonds now there's
one more thing that i'd like to do
before the end of today's video and i
want to show a bit of christmas cheer i
was thinking to myself how is santa
claus and there must be a santa claus on
the hermitcraft server how is santa
claus going to deliver his presence if i
don't have a chimney sure i've got this
tunnel but
santa claus is probably a worse flyer
than me right so
i'm thinking i'm gonna add a little
christmas tree right here and then i'm
gonna add a
temporary chimney so that he can deliver
my presents
so let's make a little custom tree
nothing too fancy i haven't made a
christmas tree in so long i haven't even
put up my christmas tree in real life
yet let alone doing it in minecraft
if only i had some of the gems left i
could use them as baubles
now making custom trees isn't actually
too difficult the key that a lot of
people seem to forget is that you need
to leave a bit of a gap between the
leaves and the center of the tree
because leaves in reality don't really
grow that close to the tree they kind of
grow exactly where the sunlight is
because in here there's technically
shade so you just gotta try and mimic
real life create a ring around the
bottom half especially when you're doing
something like a christmas tree and then
you work your way up around in a cone
and then as you get closer to the top
then of course it can start to touch
the actual side of the tree it's just
about the rest of it that's important
there we go
and then i have no idea what this looks
like
you know what for not looking at it it
was not a bad thing so the places that i
can change is i can shave off a bit here
where i've added one too many leaves
there we go i'm missing some decorations
but that is not a bad christmas tree
i'll tell you what i could have done
differently i've only got spruce leaves
with me right now but if i was gonna
change it up i'd mix in another type of
leaf in there as well but more
importantly we need to make a fireplace
so it's made a little fireplace here
completely made out of cobblestone i
think that looks pretty decent
give it a little bit more shape here or
there i i like it to keep it nice and
cozy i'm gonna add loads of netherrack
in here i think i could add a few bits
of netherrack there as well and we could
have a big fire that looks really cool
really cozy now obviously i need an
actual chimney now so i better finish it
off this kind of thing's got me all in
the mood for christmas now it's it's
obviously starting to get around that
time i'm probably going to regret
breaking this but i do want the chimney
here to stick out quite a bit so that
santa claus may visit me now this hasn't
actually gone too much to plan but
i think as long as there's a way in
that's the main thing
there we go i think that is a decent
enough entrance let's take a little fly
around oh my goodness look at all the
mobs
anyway let's take a little step back
it looks pretty awful and that was kind
of the point it does not fit in this
build at all
it definitely needs a lot of tidying up
but i could i can fix that pretty easily
and i think that just about does it from
the inside it doesn't look too bad at
all we have a chimney and we've got a
fireplace and we've got the christmas
tree now i'm gonna wait until i can get
my hands on some gems and then we're
gonna decorate it but i think that is a
pretty good place to start this all off
in our christmas spirit there is an
entire district dedicated to the festive
season but i haven't actually got any
plans for it yet but the main thing is
here that a
person delivering presents that may or
may not wear a red suit will be able to
come down here
and deliver me gifts anyway i hope you
enjoyed watching this video i certainly
enjoyed making it
and
good
bye
ow